the thickness of the edges represents the co-authorship relationship between 2 authors. the larger the edges, the stronger the relationship

the number of edges connected to a node represents the popularity of a specific author in the research field

minimum weight = n: những người cùng làm việc với nhau trong ít nhất n công trình nghiên cứu => chỉ có một số ít nhóm tác giả cùng làm việc với nhau trong ít nhất 2 nghiên cứu khoa học, hầu hết các tác giả chỉ kết hợp trong 1 công trình nghiên cứu

- How to calculate The number of links/edges connected to each node,i.e represents the popularity of each author in the network. The nodes with highest links will be the most popular (well-known) author in the research area.

- How to calculate the size of each node, which represents the number of articles that an author involved in. Therefore, it represents the contribution/activeness of an author to some extend